

info@davidhinojosa.net

i

U 098 333 5583

in /in/david-hinojosa/



davidhinojosa.net

REFERENCES

Cesar Salazar CEO

Desvu Software csalazar@devsu.com

Julia Payul

Business Analyst WebCreek julia.payul@gmail.com

Carlos Guerrero

CEO

Latinmanagers

car los. guerrero@latinmanagers.com.ec

SKILLS

Branding Editorial Web Design User Experience **UI** Design Prototyping HTML5 CSS3 SASS Javascript Wordpress Adobe CC Sketch Affinity GitHub **Project Management** Bilingüe (Ingles)

SUMMARY

I am a nationaly recognized consultant in User Experience (UX) based in Ecuador. I specialize in User Centered Design, Information Architecture and Interface Design for mobile devices and desktop. Also I have extensive knowledge of Frontend Development with HTML and CSS. I live in Quito-Ecuador but work worldwide.

WORK EXPERIENCE (8 YEARS)

Webcreek Tech

UX UI Designer / Frontend Developer 2018 - today

Devsu Software

UX UI Designer 2015 - 2017

Latinmanagers

Senior Web Designer 2014 - 2015 **SECAP**

Multimedia Designer 2012 - 2013

Creactivo Studio

Junior Web Designer 2012

Freelance Designer

Diseño Web / Fotografía 2009 - 2014

EDUCATION

- Interaction Design Foundation (User Experience Designer) 2018 Today
- Instituto de Artes Visuales Quito (Diseño Gráf co y Multimedia) 2009 2012 Quito-Ecuador (Mejor Egresado)
- George Gershwin Conservatory (Clasical Guitar) 2006-2008 Quito-Ecuador
- Nacional Conservatory of Music (Piano, Guitar and Notation) 2007 -2008 Quito-Ecuador
- E.S.P.E. (Language English) 2005 2006 Quito- Ecuador (100% Bilingual)
- Palm Beach Gardens High School 1996 2001 Florida-USA
- Watkins Middle School 1995-1996 Florida-USA
- Colegio San Gabriel 1994-1995 Quito-Ecuador
- Pensionado Universitario 1988-1994 Quito-Ecuador



CERTIFICATIONS

| Course | Date | Place |
|--|-------------------------|-----------------------------------|
| User Experience: The Beginner's Guide | January 2019 (Coursing) | The Interaction Design Foundation |
| Design thinking : The Beginner's Guide | January 2019 (Coursing) | The Interaction Design Foundation |
| Active member IDF | November 2018 | The Interaction Design Foundation |
| Build a Custom Wordpress Theme | September 2017 | Sitepoint |
| Thinking UX | Agosto 2017 | Sitepoint |
| Build a Succesful Web Design Business | July 2017 | Sitepoint |
| Digital Marketing Tools | February 2017 | San Francisco University of Quito |
| Cracking the Case With Flexbox | November 2016 | Code School |
| You, Me and SVG | November 2016 | Code School |
| Adventures in Web Animations | November 2016 | Code School |
| JavaScript Road Trip | November 2016 | Code School |
| Advertising Fundamentals | August 2016 | Lynda.com |
| Sass Essential Training | August 2016 | Lynda.com |
| UX Design Techniques | August 2016 | Lynda.com |
| JavaScript Essential Training | July 2016 | Lynda.com |

AWARDS

Best Graduate of Institute of Visual Arts Quito (IAVQ)

Visit me at

http://davidhinojosa.net